The Wild, Wild West has never been wilder...beautiful babes...bashful cowboys!
Tonight for Sure is a comedy, western film directed by Francis Ford Coppola.
Francis Ford Coppola’s feature debut blends footage from his student
short The Peeper and Jerry Schafer’s The Wide Open Spaces.
In a Sunset Strip burlesque club, a miner and a moralist plot an explosion at midnight,
sharing tales of desire and hypocrisy as they drink and watch the show.
Benjamin Jabowski, played by Karl Schanzer.
Samuel Hill, played by Don Kenney.
Lucy Mae, played by Marli Renfro.
Tonight for Sure is a 1962 American sexploitation comedy film
directed by Francis Ford Coppola and Jerry Schafer.
It was Coppola's feature directorial debut and combined two existing projects: an unreleased Western-themed nudie cutie
directed by Schafer called The Wide Open Spaces and a short film directed by Coppola called The Peeper.
The cast features Playboy cover girl Marli Renfro.
The score was composed by Coppola's father Carmine
Coppola and the cinematography by Jack Hill.
The film explores themes of nightclub, miner, sexploitation, las vegas, desert.
The tone is lighthearted.